Guide to the Matthew F. McHugh papers, 1974-1992.
McHugh, Matthew F papers
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 05, 1979 - 1983 (Box 125)
  Farmer’s Home Administration Southern Tier Homes, Secretary Bergland Trip to District, NYS Food Safety & Inspection Service, World Food Council, Food Stamps Shelter Deduction, D of Agriculture: School Lunch, D of Agriculture: Nutrition Reorganization, Conservation, Food Stamp Fraud, Binghamton June 1982 Farm Bureau Meeting, Soil conservation Service FY 1983 Budget, Dairy 50¢ per 100 weight Access, Farm Credit Administration, Ulster County Realtors Meeting Oct 1982, Tioga County: Dairy Hauling, Life Support Centers, NARAL (pro) Abortion, Right to Life, Roe v Wade Decision Jan 1973, Abortion, Poultry & Eggs: Avian Influenza Nov 1983, Egg Producers 1982, Feeding Programs, Soil Erosion, Casein, WIC Effectiveness, Sullivan County Eggs, Delaware County Dairy Programs, Food & Nutrition Services FY 1982, Food Stamps & Strikers, Reconstituted Milk, NYS Rural Farmworkers Meeting May 1981, Growers June 1981, Delaware County Dairy Farmers Mar 1979, Poultry Farmers Meeting April 1985, Dairy Scientist Awards, Farmers Home Administration Loan Guarantee Eastern Milk Producers, Carl Brink & Farm Bureau April 1980, Farmer Bureau Meeting April 1981, Dairy Price Support Aug 1980, Surplus Cheese Distribution Feb 1982 (2 files), Dairy Price Supports, Agricultural Stabilization & Conservation Service Soil Conservation 1981, Feb 1982 Appointment with Ed Melby, Affirmative Action, Democratic Caucus Report on Small Business, Federal Crop Insurance Corporation, Agricultural Appropriations FY 1983 (9 files).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 06, 1983 - 1984 (Box 120)
  Federal Trade Commission Credit Practices, FmHA Section 515 Housing/NYS Rental Assistance Program, FmHA/USDA Loan Guarantee for Center Ithaca/Rothschilds/Iszards, Biotech Appointment with Robert Barker from Cornell, 1984, NYSEG Appointment re HR 4402 Electric Consumers Protection Act 1983, Agriculture Appropriations, President’s Hunger Task Force 1984, NYS Foster Grandparent Program 1983, Wage Rate and Apple Growers, House/Senate Conference on Agricultural Appropriations FY 1984, MFM Amendment re Food Stamps, Monthly Reporting and Retrospective Budgetting in Food Stamps Amendment, Africa Supplemental PL 480 Urgent and Emergency Supplementary Funding FY 1984, Food and Nutrition Services Hearing 1983, FmHA FY 1984 Hearings, District Budget Hearings FY 1984, WIC FY 1984, Rural Electrification Administration FY 1984, Overview / Agricultural Outlook, Farm Credit Association, Agricultural Stabilization & Conservation Service, Agricultural Research Service, Animal & Plant Health Insection Service (APHIS), Foreign Agriculture Service and PL 480, Extension Services, LUCEY, Robert, Cornell Agriculture School, BLOCK, John, Secretary of Agriculture, Soil & Water Conservation, Rural Electrification, WPPSS (Whoops!), and RESNICK, Harry.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 07, 1984 - 1985 (Box 273)
  Appropriate Technology, Honey Containers 1985, Environment & Energy Study Conference 1984, Appalachian Regional Commission, Army Corps of Engineers, D of Defense, Disaster Relief Amendments, EDA Jobs Bills, Federal Energy Assistance, Energy Research Competition, Environmental Votes, Environmental Protection Agency NYS, EPA Projects, FEMA (3 files), Federal Register - General, FDA Standards (Dr. Ishay), Federal Energy Regulation Commission (2 files), Federal Procurement, Federal Surplus Property, Flooding Susquehanna River, Flood Insurance, Hazardous Waste, Hospital Regulations for Medicare, Health & Human Services (2 files), Highway & Bridge Projects, Historic Places Mational Register, Hisoric Preservation (2 files), Housing & Urban Development (7 files).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 08, 1989 - 1992 (Box 173)
  Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies, Appropriations Bill Conference Notes 1990, Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies Sub-Committee FY 1989, Agriculture FY 1991, Agriculture FY 1992.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 09, 1989 - 1990 (Box 242)
  FY 1991 Foreign Operations IBM Supercomputer Export, Syracuse Hearing Select Committee Children, Youth, & Families 7/90, Energy & Water FY 1990 West Valley, Labor, Health, Human Services NYS Nousing Demo 7/89, Office of Personnel Management - Broome/Tioga Wage Rates, Climate Centers (2 files), Associate Expert Project, Agriculture Conference & Continuing Resolution FY 1987, Conference Agriculture FY 1987, Vestal Levee Authorization 10/1986, Wegmans Tax Provisions 11/87, Stewart Airport 1987, Supplemental McHugh Amendment FY 1989, Cornell Plant Protection Programs 1987, Broome County Airport Landfill 01/91, WIC Transcript Certification Letter Lawsuit, Appropriations - Agriculture Markup Notes FY 1984, Ulster - Woodstock Asbestos 7/86, Cornell - National Science Foundation High Tech 12/84, NYS Trade Adjustment Assistance Centers (TAAC) 9/89.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 10, 1989 - 1993 (Box 169)
  Fiscal Year 1992, Fiscal Year 1993, Fiscal Year 1993, Fiscal Year 1989.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 11, 1976 - 1993 (Box 170)
  HR 9719 Payments in Lieu of Taxes 1976, Agriculture Conference Report FY 1993, Livestock Liability Amendment 1976-1978, Agriculture Conference FY 1991, Agriculture Appropriations FY 1990.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 12 (Box 174)
  HR 2698 Agriculture House/Senate Conference Notes FY 1992, Agriculture FY 1992 (5" thick file).
- Cabinet Department Files Issues Files, 1978 - 1985 (Box 281)
  EPA & Noise Standards, Hazardous Materials Disposal/Transport, Energy Conservation, Parkland Payment in lieu of taxes, Whip Legislative Reports 1978, USDA Soil Conservation, USDA, Farmer’s Home Administration, D of Defense, Army Corps of Engineer, D of Commerce, National Demonstration Water Project, EPA New Source Performance Standards, FED Energy Administration, Energy Inventions, HEW - Education, D of Energy, Federal Communications Commission (2 files), Federal Trade Commission, D of Justice, D of Health & Human Services, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, Housing and Urban Development, D of Labor (2 files), National Endowment for Arts & Humanities, Funding for Fire Departments, US Postal Service, D of Interior, Small Business Administration (2 files), Small Business Investments, Small Business Conference, National Science Foundation, Health and Human Services Cuban/Haitian Refugees, Regional Commissions, Recreation Programs, D of Defense Selling to the Military, 70001 Program, Technology Transfer Center, Tent Caterpillars, Transportation Programs, NYS D of Transportation, D of Transportation Buy & Sell Rule, D of Treasury, D of Treasury Bureau of Alcohol Tobacco and Firearms, Veteran’s Administration, Federal Register Updates June 1981-April 1982.
- Campaign Materials, 1978, 1979, 1980, 1982, 1985 (Box 284)
  Assorted Campaign Materials.
- Campaign Materials, 1978 - 1988 (Box 157)
  McHugh Schedules 1984, McHugh Schedules 1985, McHugh Schedules 1986, Campaign Reports, Report by John Mennell, Friends of Matt McHugh, Class of 1982, Budgets 1978-1988, Campaign Critique, Federal Election Commission Report 1977, Federal Election Commission Report 1978, Federal Election Commission Report 1979, Federal Election Commission Report 1980, Campaign Strategy 1990, Campaign Plan “Past”, Campaign Plan 1986, Campaign Plan 1988, Media 1984-1988.
- Campaign Materials, 1983 - 1984 (Box 24)
  Press Clippings by month, 1983-1984, Folder by Press Outlet (large WDST folders), "Irish" and "EPA Horrors" files..
- Campaign Materials, 1984 - 1990 (Box 159)
  2 shoebox-sized boxes, (1) Seven 1986 Reel-to-Reel Endorsement Tapes, (2) Eight 1990 Reel-to-Reel Radio Buy tapes, Folders, 1984 Schedules, Campaign Information: wide date range, 1986-1990 Releases (just a few), 1986 District Schedules.
- Campaign Materials, 1984 - 1990 (Box 160)
  4 shoebox-sized boxes, (1) Cassette Tapes: 1984 (Connie Cook & MFM at various venues), (2) Cassette Tapes: Random, four labelled empty, (3) McHugh for Congress Bumper Stickers, (4) Five Reel-to-Reel one minute spots from 1990.
- Campaign Materials, 1986 - 1991 (Box 158)
  Assorted Campaign materials..
- Cassette Tapes (Box 270)
- Conference & Travel Documentation, 1979 (Box 99)
  Trips to district, town meetings, etc..
- Conference & Travel Documentation, 1979, 1985, 1986, 1991 (Box 26)
  Nicaragua 1979, Turkish Border 1991, Japan 1985, Mid-East 1985 (folders for Israel, Syria, Jordan, Egypt), EIA Conference at Captiva FL 1986, Guatemala 1985.
- Conference & Travel Documentation, 1979 - 1980 (Box 240)
  Background materials for, (1) Middle East trip to Israel, Egypt, Tunisia, (2) Pakistan, (3) African/Amercian Conference at Hot Springs VA.
- Conference & Travel Documentation, 1979 - 1992 (Box 263)
  House Delegation to USSR Trip Report Apr 1979, House Foreign Affairs Committee Nicaragua Trip Nov 1979, US Relations w/ Central?Eastern Europe (Vienna) 1992, Center for Strategic & International Studies Trip Mainland China Feb 1984 (Binder & Three Files), US/USSR IOnterparliamentary Delegation Briefing Book Mar 1985, US Presidential Elections 92 Barcelona, Central American Trip Feb 1983 (7 files), Far East/Southeast Asia Jun 1977 (Binder/Report), Guatemala 1985, Near East 1980, McHugh authored Policy Papers interspersed.
- Conference & Travel Documentation, 1982 - 1990 (Box 260)
  Central American Trip Jun 1984, Germany/Vienna Trip Jul 1989, Intelligence Trip Apr 1990, Jordan/India/Nepal Jan 1984, USSR Jul 1983, West Coast Jul 1984, Warsaw/Krakow Mar 1982 (two files).
- Conference & Travel Documentation, 1984 - 1990 (Box 256)
  US/USSR Relations Conference (Jamaica) Jan 1989, US/USSR European Relations (Dubrovnick) Aug/Sep 1989, El Salvador Feb 1990, Eastern Europe/Ireland Aug 1990, Democratic Issues Conference (Greenbrier) Dec 1989, Italy/Jordan/India/Nepal Jan 1984, China Feb 1984, Personal Vacation (Aspen) Aug/Sep 1989, Cancelled Costa Rica, Cancelled Jamaica 1989.
- Conference & Travel Documentation, 1987 - 1988 (Box 3)
  Strasbourg Conference, Central America Trip, Aspen Institute at Montego Bay, Aspen Institute at Switzerland.
- Conference & Travel Documentation, Various (Box 272)
  Poland 1982, England/Saudi Arabia/ Paksitan/India 1980, USSR 1979 (two files), Israel1988, Strasbourg 1987 (four files), Aspen Institute Jamaica 1991, Aspen Institute Ireland 1991, El Salvador 1990, Aspen Institute on USSR 1 Jamaica 1987, Aspen Institute on USSR 2 Switzerland 1987, Aspen Institute on USSR 3 Jamaica 1988.
- Constituent "Please Help" files, circa 1984 (Box 87)
  Labelled by federal agency & constituent.
- Correspondence - Alpha 094-1, 1975 - 1976 (Box 224)
  AA - EZ.
- Correspondence - Alpha 094-2, 1975 - 1976 (Box 206)
  FA - KZ.
- Correspondence - Alpha 094-3, 1975 - 1976 (Box 216)
  LAA - RZ.
- Correspondence - Alpha 094-4, 1975 - 1976 (Box 200)
  SAA - ZZ.
- Correspondence - Alpha 095-1, 1976 - 1978 (Box 135)
  A - E.
- Correspondence - Alpha 095-2, 1976 - 1978 (Box 43)
  F - G - H.
- Correspondence - Alpha 095-3, 1976 - 1978 (Box 47)
  H - I - J - K - L - Mc - M - N - O.
- Correspondence - Alpha 095-4, 1975 - 1978 (Box 148)
  P - SS.
- Correspondence - Alpha 095-5, 1976 - 1978 (Box 136)
  STA - W.
- Correspondence - Alpha 095-6, 1976 - 1978 (Box 111)
  WAA - Z.
- Correspondence - General A01, January - March 1979 (Box 36)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 00001-01400.
- Correspondence - General A02, March 1979 (Box 133)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 01401 - 03376.
- Correspondence - General A03, April 1979 (Box 32)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 03377-06450.
- Correspondence - General A04, April - June 1979 (Box 142)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 06451 - 08800.
- Correspondence - General A05, June 1979 (Box 41)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 08001 - 10650.
- Correspondence - General A06, June - August 1979 (Box 144)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 10651 - 12475.
- Correspondence - General A07, August 1979 (Box 37)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 12476-14325.
- Correspondence - General A08, October - November 1979 (Box 38)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 14326-15950.
- Correspondence - General A09, November 1979 (Box 140)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 15951 - 16500.
- Correspondence - General A10, December 1979 - January 1980 (Box 40)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 16501-18500.
- Correspondence - General A11, January - March 1980 (Box 143)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 18501 - 20400.
- Correspondence - General A12, October 1979 - April 1980 (Box 33)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 20401 - 22000.
- Correspondence - General A13, April - May 1980 (Box 149)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 22001 - 23475.
- Correspondence - General A14, May - June 1980 (Box 141)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 23476 - 24900.
- Correspondence - General A15, June - July 1980 (Box 45)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 24901 - 26100.
- Correspondence - General A16, July - August 1980 (Box 49)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 26101 - 27800.
- Correspondence - General A17, September - October 1980 (Box 42)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 27801 - 29400.
- Correspondence - General A19, November 1980 - January 1981 (Box 138)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 29951 - 32300.
- Correspondence - General A20, January - March 1981 (Box 35)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 32301-34200.
- Correspondence - General A21, April - May 1981 (Box 39)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 34201-36000.
- Correspondence - General A22, April 1981 (Box 68)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 36001 - 39000.
- Correspondence - General A23, April 1981 (Box 117)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 39001 - 39800.
- Correspondence - General A24, March - June 1981 (Box 185)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 39801 - 41725.
- Correspondence - General A25, June - August 1981 (Box 69)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 41726 - 43275.
- Correspondence - General A26, August - October 1981 (Box 74)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 43276 - 45400.
- Correspondence - General A27, September - November 1981 (Box 86)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 45401 - 47225.
- Correspondence - General A28, October 1981 - January 1982 (Box 60)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 47226 - 49200.
- Correspondence - General A29, January 1982 (Box 122)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 49201 - 50426.
- Correspondence - General A41, January - February 1983 (Box 226)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 65001 - 67200.
- Correspondence - General A42, February - April 1983 (Box 202)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 67201 - 69300.
- Correspondence - General A43, April - May 1983 (Box 219)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 69301 - 71051.
- Correspondence - General A44, June - July 1983 (Box 204)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 71101 - 72950.
- Correspondence - General A45, June - August 1983 (Box 215)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 72951 - 74900.
- Correspondence - General A46, August - October 1983 (Box 227)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 74901 - 76400.
- Correspondence - General A47, October - November 1983 (Box 205)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 76401 - 77750.
- Correspondence - General A48, November 1983 (Box 218)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 77751 - 78550.
- Correspondence - General A49, October 1983 - February 1984 (Box 52)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 78551-80000.
- Correspondence - General A50, February - March 1984 (Box 51)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 80001-81400.
- Correspondence - General A51, March 1984 (Box 66)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 81401 - 83100.
- Correspondence - General A52, March - June 1984 (Box 76)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 83101 - 84200.
- Correspondence - General A53, June - August 1984 (Box 78)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 84201 - 86950.
- Correspondence - General A54, August - October 1984 (Box 79)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 85951 - 87300.
- Correspondence - General A55, September - December 1984 (Box 129)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 87301 - 89250.
- Correspondence - General A56, December 1984 - February 1985 (Box 62)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 89251 - 90400.
- Correspondence - General A57, February - April 1985 (Box 110)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 90401 - 92250.
- Correspondence - General A58, March - May 1985 (Box 88)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 92251 - 93900.
- Correspondence - General A59, May - July 1985 (Box 131)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 93901 - 95750.
- Correspondence - General A60, July 1985 (Box 50)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 95751 - 97100.
- Correspondence - General A61, August - December 1985 (Box 211)
  Correspondence Log Sequence A, 97101 - 98900.
- Correspondence - General B01, January - August 1986 (Box 222)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 00001 - 01500.
- Correspondence - General B02, January - February 1986 (Box 236)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 01551 - 02350.
- Correspondence - General B03, February - March 1986 (Box 214)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 02351 - 03650.
- Correspondence - General B04, March - April 1986 (Box 213)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 03651 - 04600.
- Correspondence - General B05, January - April 1986 (Box 235)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 04601 - 06000.
- Correspondence - General B06, February - June 1986 (Box 228)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 06001 - 06650.
- Correspondence - General B08, December 1985 - September 1986 (Box 301)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 09151 - 10200.
- Correspondence - General B09, September - October 1986 (Box 176)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 10201 - 11450.
- Correspondence - General B10, September 1986 - January 1987 (Box 303)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 11451 - 12600.
- Correspondence - General B11, January 1987 (Box 25)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 12601-13000.
- Correspondence - General B12, January - March 1987 (Box 13)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 13001-14150.
- Correspondence - General B13, February - April 1987 (Box 18)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 14151-15550.
- Correspondence - General B14, April - May 1987 (Box 1)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 15551 - 16400.
- Correspondence - General B16, July - August 1987 (Box 302)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 17751 - 18350.
- Correspondence - General B18, October - November 1987 (Box 17)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 19901-20700.
- Correspondence - General B25, March - April 1988 (Box 179)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 22701 - 23800.
- Correspondence - General B26, April 1988 (Box 306)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 23801 - 24500.
- Correspondence - General B27, March - May 1988 (Box 180)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 24501 - 26650.
- Correspondence - General B28, May - June 1988 (Box 307)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 26651 - 27500.
- Correspondence - General B29, May - July 1988 (Box 178)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 27501 - 28650.
- Correspondence - General B30, July - August 1988 (Box 305)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 28651 - 29550.
- Correspondence - General B31, September - November 1988 (Box 261)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 29551 - 30700.
- Correspondence - General B32, October - December 1988 (Box 304)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 30701 - 31600.
- Correspondence - General B33, December 1988 - February 1989 (Box 293)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 31601 - 32550.
- Correspondence - General B34, February - March 1989 (Box 292)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 32551 - 33400.
- Correspondence - General B35, March - April 1989 (Box 241)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 33401 - 34600.
- Correspondence - General B36, April - July 1989 (Box 264)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 34601 - 35600.
- Correspondence - General B37, April - June 1989 (Box 248)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 35601 - 37300.
- Correspondence - General B38, June - September 1989 (Box 30)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 37301-38750.
- Correspondence - General B39, September - November 1989 (Box 29)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 38751-40000.
- Correspondence - General B40, November 1989 - January 1990 (Box 28)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 40001-41150.
- Correspondence - General B41, January - March 1990 (Box 27)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 41151-42200.
- Correspondence - General B42, April 1990 (Box 23)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 42201-43400.
- Correspondence - General B43, April - May 1990 (Box 22)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 43401-44500.
- Correspondence - General B44, July 1990 (Box 21)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 44501-45900.
- Correspondence - General B45, July 1990 (Box 20)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 45901-47050.
- Correspondence - General B46, September 1990 (Box 19)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 47051-48250.
- Correspondence - General B47, October - December 1990 (Box 16)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 48251-49200.
- Correspondence - General B48, December 1990 (Box 15)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 49201-49700.
- Correspondence - General B49, January - March 1991 (Box 14)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 49701-50700.
- Correspondence - General B50, March - April 1991 (Box 11)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 50701-51800.
- Correspondence - General B51, April - June 1991 (Box 12)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 51801-52800.
- Correspondence - General B52, June - July 1991 (Box 9)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 52801-53950.
- Correspondence - General B53, July - August 1991 (Box 8)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 53951-55050.
- Correspondence - General B54, August - November 1991 (Box 7)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 55051-56350.
- Correspondence - General B55, November 1991 - February 1992 (Box 6)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 56351-57750.
- Correspondence - General B56, February 1992 (Box 10)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 57751-58950.
- Correspondence - General B57, April - May 1992 (Box 294)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 58951 - 60000.
- Correspondence - General B58, March - August 1992 (Box 291)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 60001 - 61250.
- Correspondence - General B59, August - December 1992 (Box 297)
  Correspondence Log Sequence B, 61251 - 62000.
- Correspondence by Topic, 1979 - 1992 (Box 243)
  Binghamton Dairy Hearing 6/85, Binghamton Dairy Hearing Witness Requests, Agricultural Appropriations FY 1987, Ulster - Hospitals Rural/Urban Medicare Reimbursement 4/87, McHugh Budget Substitute 4/84, D of Agriculture Enforcement of Kosher Meat Standards 12/83, D of Agriculture - WIC Rebates, McHugh Energy Tax Legislation I & II c1979 (2 files), Meeting with Secretary Duncan 9/79, Home Energy Price Relief Act of 1979 Fact Sheet, Home Energy Price Relief Act of 1979 Cost Estimates, Salina Nuclear, Business & Taxes Alternative Measures, Balanced Budget Constitutional Amendment 7/82, Energy - Home Heating Oil and Gas, Wind Energy Conference 9/81, Democratic Caucus Revised Rules 11/82, HJR 637 Equal Rights Amendment Extension of Ratification Deadline 8/78, Agriculture - WIC Reallocations 8/82, Agriculture - WIC Reallocations NYS Problems 6/84, Energy & Water FY 1986 Binghamton First Ward Levee, Broome - Vestal Levee, HUD Technical Assistance Grants FY 1985 Appropriations, Drug & Substance Abuse Conference 2/85, Woodstock Sewer Refinancing, Labor, Health, Human Serices FY 1992 Cornell ILR Workplace Center Earmarks, Labor, Health, Human Serices FY 1985 Cornell Resources Center, Children & Youth, NYS Monthly Reporting & Retrospective Budget Waiver 1/84.
- Correspondence by Topic (Box 64)